Caleb Sanders

(530) 526-9189 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/caleb-sanders-wd/ | 97caleb.sanders@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://calebsanders.herokuapp.com/

Professional Summary

Excellent work history in positions requiring responsibility, initiative, accuracy and confidentiality. Ability to interface effectively with management. Hard working and dedicated to meet the standards expected for the job. Main area of expertise focused around the design and development of websites.

Technical Skills

CSS, HTML5, JavaScript, C#, NodeJS + ExpressJS Java, Android, ES6, AngularJS, React MongoDB, ASP.NET MVC, Ruby

Experience

❖ DealerSocket

Neumont Collaborative Project Externship

Draper, UT | April 2018 - Present

- Working on automating data analysis for the company's focus on CRM. In the process, we will be saving the company hundreds of thousands of dollars and many hours of development.
- Tribal D, Inc. Native American Self Governance

Neumont Collaborative Project Externship

North Salt Lake, UT | January 2018 – March 2018:

- Made updates to the user interface for field updates by module, reports, grid controls, emails. Created new item types within the database model.
- Student Ambassador

Neumont College of Computer Science

Salt Lake City, UT | February 2017 – September 2017

 The purpose as an ambassador was to welcome prospective students considering enrollment. Including answering any questions a family may have as well as promoting the school to the families.

Project Highlights

- Capstone Project Frank Florez House Cleaning
 - Over the course of ten weeks, I designed and a fully-fledged e-commerce site for my previous employer. The site allows the user to easily generate a service order for house cleaning online. Developed using NodeJS/ExpressJS, AngularJS, EJS, and Google OAuth.
- Advanced Web Scripting Final Activity Hunt
 - This SPA serves to allow users to find activities to do regardless of the weather outside. The purpose of this application is to solve the issue of boredom we experience in our everyday lives. Developed using AngularJS and Google Maps API.
- Web Based Software Projects Talon
 - This application serves as a stats tracker for the popular video game Overwatch by Blizzard Entertainment. This application implements an unofficial API for all player data. Developed using ASP.NET MVC and SQL.

Education

Bachelors of Science, Web Design and Development

Neumont College of Computer Science – Salt Lake City, UT – August, 2018

Additional Information

Volunteer Work:

- VFW Post #4218, Corning, CA:
 - o January 2006 September 2015
- CSF, Red Bluff High School, Red Bluff, CA:
 - o September 2011 June 2015